<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Utility_app</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="hi">Hi</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="privacy">Privacy Policy
Updated at 2022-11-02
Utility ("we," "our," or "us") is committed to protecting your privacy This Privacy Policy explains how your personal information is
collected, used, and disclosed by utility.
This Privacy Policy applies to our application named utility , and its associated subdomains (collectively, our "Service"). By accessing
or using our Service, you signify that you have read, understood, and agree to our collection, storage, use, and disclosure of your
personal information as described in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service
Definitions and key terms
To help explain things as clearw as possible in this Privacy Policy, every time any of these terms are referenced, are strict\'/ defined
• Cookie: small amount of data generated by a website and saved by your web browser It is used to identify your browser,
provide anatytics, remember information about you such as your language preference or login information.
• Company: when this policy mentions "Company," "we," "us,' or •our,' it refers to utility, Tamil Nadu that is responsible for your
information under this Privacy Policy
• Country: where utility or the owners,'founders of utility are based, in this case is India
• Customer: refers to the company, organization or person that signs up to use the utility Service to manage the relationships
with your consumers or service users.
• Device: any intemet connected device such as a phone, tablet, computer or any other device that can be used to visit Utility
and use the services.
• IP address: Every device connected to the Intemet is assigned a number known as an Intemet protocol address These
numbers are usually assigned in geographic blocks An IP address can often be used to identify the location from which a
device is connecting to the Internet
• Personnel: refers to those individuals who are employed by utility or are under contract to perform a service on behalf of one
of the parties
• Personal Data: any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information — including a personal
identification number — allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person
• Service: refers to the service provided by utility as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this platform.
Third-party service: refers to advertisers, contest sponsors, promotional and marketing partners, and others who provide our
content or whose products or services we think may interest ',nou_
• Website: Utility's site, which can be accessed via this URL:
• You: a person or entity that is registered with Utility to use the Services
        What Information Do We Collect?
We collect information from you when you visit our service, register, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey
or fill out a form.
Name / Username
• Phone Numbers
• Email Addresses
Mailing Addresses
Billing Addresses
Debit\credit card numbers
• Password
We also collect information from mobile devices for a better user experience, although these features are completely optional:
• Location (GPS): Location data Location data helps to create an accurate representation of your interests, and this can be used
to bring more targeted and relevant ads to potential customers.
How Do We Use The Information We Collect?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
• To improve our service (we continualty strive to improve our service offerings based on the information and feedbackwe receive
from you)
• To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectivety respond to your customer service requests and
support needs)
To process transactions
• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
• To send periodic emails
When do we use customer information from third
parties?
We receive some information from the third parties when you contact u. For example, when you submit your email address to us to
shov.' interest in becoming our customer, we receive information from a third party that provides automated fraud detection services to
us. We also occasionallv collect information that is made oubliclv available on social media websites. You can control how much of
        your information social media websites make public by visiting these websites and changing your privacy settings
Do we share the information we collect with third
parties?
We may share the information that we collect, both personal and non-personal, with third parties such as advertisers, contest
sponsors, promotional and marketing partners, and others who provide our content or whose products or services we think may
interest you. We may also share it with our current and future affiliated companies and business partners, and ifwe are involved in a
merger, asset sale or other business reorganization, we may also share or transfer your personal and non-personal information to our
successors-in-interestisi:i
We may engage trusted third party service providers to perform functions and provide services to us, such as hosting and
maintaining our servers and our service, database storage and management, e-mail management, storage marketing, credit card
processing, customer service and fulfilling orders for products and services you may purchase through our service We will likely
share your personal information, and possibly some non-personal information, with these third parties to enable them to perform
these services for us and for
We may share portions of our log file data, including IP addresses, for analytics purposes with third parties such as web analytics
partners, application developers, and ad nebuorks_ If your IP address is shared, it may be used to estimate general location and other
technographics such as connection speed, whether you have visited the service in a shared location, and type of device used to visit
the service. They may aggregate information about our advertising and what you see on the service and then provide auditing,
research and reporting for us and our advertisers
We may also disclose personal and non-personal information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties
as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in order to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to
protect our rights and interests or those of a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical,
or legally actionable activity, or to othemqse comply wdh applicable court orders, laws, rules and regulations.
Where and when is information collected from
customers and end users?
We will collect personal information that you submit to u. We may also receive personal information about you from third parties as
described above.
        How Do We Use Your Email Address?
By submitting your email address on our service, you agree to receive emails from u. You can cancel your participation in any of
these email lists at any time by clicking on the opt-out link or other unsubscribe option that is included in the respective email. We
only send emails to people who have authorized us to contact them, either directty, or through a third party We do not send
unsolicited commercial emails, because we hate spam as much as you dc By submitting your email address, you also agree to allow
us to use your email address for customer audience targeting on sites like Facebook, where we display custom advertising to specific
people who have opted-in to receive communications from u. Email addresses submitted only through the order processing page
will be used for the sole purpose of sending you information and updates pertaining to your order If, however, you have provided the
same email to us through another method, we may use it for any of the purposes stated in this Policy Note: If at any time you would
like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails. we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
        Links to Other Websites
This Privacy Policy applies ony to the Services. The Services may contain links to other websites not operated or controlled by us.
We are not responsible for the content, accuracy or opinions expressed in such websites, and such websites are not investigated,
monitored or checked for accuracy or completeness by us Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Services to
another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that
have a link on our platform, is subject to that website's own rules and policies. Such third parties may use their own cookies or other
methods to collect information about you
Cookies
We use "Cookies" to identity the areas of our website that you have visited A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer
or mobile device by your web browser. We use Cookies to personalize the Content that you see on our website. Most web browsers
can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access functionality on our website
correctly or at all. We never place Personally Identifiable Information in Cookie.
Payment Details
In respect to any credit card or other payment processing details you have provided us, we commit that this confidential information
will be stored in the most secure manner possible.
        Contact Us
Don't hesitate to contact us if you have any question.
Via Email: Utility_official@gmail.com
Via this Link: utility_contactus.com
    </string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="get_otp">GET OTP</string>
</resources>